[Music]
the 80s which dot or it or the game
guiding hot system
she's checking if your mom asks you to
do something and if you don't do it
immediately she will do something worth
she'll Jordan herself who said that joke
who should have won best mentor on
comic-con instead of the wind Richard
the best best mentor award should've
gone to Penny Sousa very good if
anything does didn't just teach us the
skill of improv she taught us humanity
[Applause]
[Music]
guys welcome to the journal fun games at
Five Guys as you know this is the
general fun game show and today we have
some really exciting yes and these
contestants are gonna be tested on
skills that they had never had before
and they're going to discover these
skills within them and then they're
gonna be like why did I come on the show
and I'll be like Julie just edited it on
YouTube now it's too late
alright guys so I don't want to delay
this any further we're gonna introduce
our contestants
our first contestant whoa
is what people think when you say this
person's name and when I say I want you
guys to go oh yeah he likes to play
badminton and in the spare time he does
comedy I think I don't you say anymore
cuz you guys obviously know who I'm
talking about
we put your hands together or as they
wore at the same time for our first
contestant for the finish
[Applause]
our next contestant is a wonderful human
being I made it for two years and I
remember being like you're gonna go far
and and then and then I created the game
show after I met her and now she's here
and I think I don't know how much
further you can go then being on the
game show like this is a peek you guys
have peeked this is it after this
written comedy huh you're quitting
comedy out of it he actually makes boho
south boohoo serials for real they got a
joke she does so I expect a lot of drama
from her today our last contestant now
this guy when I met him he was very
memorable like I don't remember mentally
but like with my heart season my heart
like remembers him anyway it is not only
a blessing or a door
but also it no it is a blessing it sits
in the doors we have him on the show
please put your hands together for the
very awesome the Texans you know how the
game show up there for round and you're
gonna begin with the first roster are
you ready
always guys we're gonna start with the
first round and the first song is called
rapidly general how father you're only
yeah
question number one this is the general
fun game show season 2 which means that
there was a season one I'm even one they
want an episode five just like you guys
are a Passat five right now who wore the
contestants on season 1 episode 5
yes socket on yes
son is it good yes no I'm afraid but you
almost got it right it yes for Chucky
dr. Cenarion Jose no none of the
positive watch me socket
Zacchaeus and Ally and also Ronan no no
you gotta get this shot did I could try
song kid Sonali and Suppan wanna know
does anyone in the audience have the
answer you mother
[Applause]
[Music]
audience yeah okay fantastic
you get ten points but you get to pass
your ten points to anyone the
contestants in many theaters within
touching a [__] bar the game going
hot all right the next question what
movie does the following song come from
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
next question who it was a very tough
question and I also want to know why and
there's only one correct answer for this
question but should have one shot see
pets fur what all right I've got the by
[__] shop Rashad who should've won
been mentored serve Naveen Richard on
comics on season one and why the best
best mentor award should have gone to
Connie Sutra and the reason for which is
[Laughter]
[Applause]
do what we practice you
all right the next question and this is
a very tough one so listen carefully
what is hmm 5 times 5 divided by 1 times
5 divided by 5 divided by 5 divided by 1
times 5 yes how 35 for our resident
mathematician whoa all right question
number 6 7 8 next question is my
question
and this is a very tough one so listen
to the full Christian list the Comic Con
judges according to their height in
descending order
who was it in descending order yeah go
don't know what descending no person is
here
fancy recording all this shop Thunder
what is it that is the correct answer
free shotty no oh yes fun yes Oh fun
Dunham a rebus aw yeah Vernon Kenny yeah
Denise yeah naveen thank you thank you
moving on to the last question the last
question of this evening one of my
favorite movies of the questions one of
my favorite movies is Kuch Kuch Hota Hai
in ten words can you be describe the
story of Kuch Kuch Hota Hai
[Music]
[Applause]
would you leave then in the next
question you all get to answer the
question but you have to do it in
accents in - Ahn soo-ji show the accents
the audience be please explain our
integrity hi sorrow can apply backup
plan pay I'll feed you 20 points in a
shot because that was a story right all
right for Jessie happy show the audience
your exit fee this place is a fifteen
one mother died either daughter cries
[Laughter]
all right you have to also ask the same
question in 15 words can you please show
the accent to the audience I don't know
how this is an accent is a union
territory you know one flaw here in
cancel after another flaw peering
unibrow mob anomic the end 1500
[Applause]
[Laughter]
all right we're gonna start without to
which is called yeah hey I've put up a
joke famous joke from comedian Indian
comedians you have to guess who said
that joke the [__] yeah
kids got jokes hey is the guy who was
with me said mei-hua for Javon Bennett
seijin make ha ha ha
yeah hi ATM killing me carajo all right
the time is up could you please reveal
your answer was tough with you rattled
or canal come lo que habrá Strathcona
I'll come right in the shot raju
actually copy this joke yeah yeah that's
it yeah yeah oh you gotta fight fight to
that mission and ten points or
Prashanthi and Rahul ah I thought this
is gonna be tough with these guys okay
joke number two is my uterus is like
have a baby and I'm like I'm trying but
the man insists are wearing condoms Joe
alright your time with a machete we'll
talk to sue could you please reveal your
answer come on
[Applause]
oh boy after this naked one oh yeah kids
got joke here number three
yeah if your mom asks you to do
something and if you don't do it
immediately she will do something worse
she'll do it herself
all right
we started uni Sha Tsui
[Applause]
[Music]
alright alright guys I am going to go
into the audience and get one word you
will then have to guess what the word is
if you do not get the word that is
written on the clipboard you have to
justify why your word is closest to that
word all right
does everyone know this game was yeah
who's never seen the gender fun game
show by the way anyone in the audience
all right guys so now
[Applause]
[Laughter]
chart the answer was not what you guys
said no one got the right word to get
the right word with nacho yeah not this
country Kjar now you guys have to chain
why your word is close to nachos in the
most creative poetic way possible you
know you however you want to your to it
we'll start with you Nashawn Howard
ladies first
boy the guide the Oxford day
why is what do you say don't want to
sound racist but tell me out like with
the bum is the food eaten by people
living south of our country yes and
nachos is eaten by people living in
south of America
yeah yeah okay so there is the South
connection and there's a snack
connection but in long-term everything
is the same
[Applause]
I find the best get the points not like
you just get points photonics
all right Rahul due August I'll go with
you why is now chose closest to chart in
addition to whatever process you said
whatever she said because yeah you can
you can know you can like for for
additional flavor you can as a chart the
[Applause]
and and and you know like if you take
like as a triangular six notch oh yeah
you put them in circle you'll not only
make a base for chart that region chart
what do you make a pie chart also why is
not your closest to bail booty what do
you say baby booty big booty carnival
oka paid cows affair yeah or not just
Ankara
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
all right guys that means we have come
to almost the end of this show but we
have one more round left and this is a
new round that I invented just for this
game oh yes and the ground is called
emoticon kahani explain and stop making
us clap all the time alright in this rod
what can happen is you guys are going to
get emoticons on the screen
you then have to make up a story using
those emoticons however this is the
general fun game show and not your
mother's house which means I'm not gonna
make it easy you have to tell us the
story but you have to do it in song
you can choose to sing there will be
music playing or you can choose to use
the music to dramatize your story and
make it come alive and pop for all the
audience watching on screen right now
and for this live audience right here
okay okay okay are you guys ready - can
you give us a demo yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
the next game show I've changed up a bit
where I'm gonna be one the contestants
are you ready we're gonna start with the
first person and the first person to
begin this is maybe Jonathan imagine you
are talking this
[Applause]
just took a spoon I was walking in the
desert
yeah I saw top he saw me and his face
turned red and his eyes big big because
I was feeling a diamond somehow he knew
me that I took drugs somehow I I tried
to convince him that I am NOT into drugs
only interested in diamonds but he was
like for like not convincing enough
can we move ahead with the story that
the end now you give us a conclusion to
the story
oh then he was confused and you know
what they say about confusion when in
doubt don't do it
[Applause]
you thought you get 40 shots - you are
up next my friend this one day I will
dress women playing table cast
- Kenny's when I stole a joint from
Bravo Dora who was best the Queen for
some reason because it's telling a
diamond and he was trying to be in
disguise
[Applause]
and then met a policeman who take
anything kuhmo
[Applause]
there was a girl with the shakers by the
way I presume is guys
you ain't it's guy with your silly
diamond yeah and then the cop said she
barbecue to the Vanara he also tried to
make him talk yeah you were appalled
that this whole story is tying in
together a weaving into alright
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
a father
[Laughter]
[Applause]
alright guys that was a very tough round
and I scored the last round out of 2086
after the third round the total scores
were nice chance to be on 101 rock on
111 I protect 101 however however after
the turn around after adding 2086 the
Tartar e rasool' have come tied at 2565
[Applause]
[Music]
but we are not going to let you go
without a gift draw our sponsors the
beautiful gift hamper the sponsor is
neat
I can i sponsor it and it place to keep
all the things from my house that I
don't want and I wrapped it up and put a
boy I got the soccer ball from some
someone some random brand thing and some
nice they from facewash
earth in the packet Ivan used the new
one yeah I also had I went on a cleanse
but then I stopped it are you ready
current date tonight smoothies they
taste like Mindy yeah like vintage and
like some pollutant it got expired
no no and then this is actually from our
prop box just to make it look more full
so we needed
I don't wear anymore
it's a lovely pair pen and it's a
plastic fruits and although our plastic
straws reusable straws for the smoothie
because this wasn't a kit last time you
may see needs resolve this is what we
find I also bought about door one I know
I'm the best
yeah and thank you can ease for proving
it to the world
finally for giving you the platform yeah
sure who you ready are ya that I love
you guys you've been a supporter to do
[Applause]